bytecolumn.com 2015-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Byte Column

This privacy policy sets out how bytecolumn.com uses and protects any information that you  
give bytecolumn.com when you use this website.  
bytecolumn.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you  
to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then  
you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
bytecolumn.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should  
check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy  
is effective from [date].  
What we collect  
We may collect the following information:  
• name and job title  
• contact information including email address  
• demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
• other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers  
What we do with the information we gather  
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service,  
and in particular for the following reasons:  
• Internal record keeping.  
• We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
• We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or  
other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address  
which you have provided.  
• From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market  
research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the  
information to customise the website according to your interests.  
Security  
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent  
unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and  
managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
How we use cookies  
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive.  
Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know  
when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an  
individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by  
gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data  
about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We  
only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from  
the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which  
pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your  
computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept  
cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  
This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.  
Links to other websites  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used  
these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other  
website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any  
information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by  
this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement  
applicable to the website in question.  
Controlling your personal information  
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following  
ways:  
• whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can  
click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct  
marketing purposes  
• if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct  
marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing  
us at contact@bytecolumn.com  
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have  
your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to  
send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find  
interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please  
write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any  
information found to be incorrect.

## Hottest Stories around the world
